

Samuel Akinyemi

+2347048706198, +2349035675659

akinyemisamuel170@gmail.com

18b, Oladipo Bakare Street, Ladipo-Ikeja GRA, Ikeja, Lagos, Nigeria.

bit.ly/samakins-portfolio in linkedin.com/in/akinyemi-samuel-927751225

Objectives

I am a certified Full-Stack Web Designer and actively building my experience in Artificial Intelligence and Robotics Engineering to integrate my IT skills into a model that will help solve real life problems facing my environment and the world at large.

Education

Federal College of Education (Technical), Akoka

Nov. 2022 NCE, Computer/Mathematics Education

- Most Outstanding 300l Computer Student 2021/2022
- Campus Fellowship Coordinator (AFCF) 2021/2022
- Overall Best 200l Computer Student 2020/2021

Masters Computer College

Sept. 2018 | Diploma, Desktop Publishing

• Expert in Microsoft Office Packages and CorelDraw.

Kolabod Private School

Aug. 2018 | High School Diploma, Science

- Senior Prefect (Head Boy) 2017/2018
- Punctuality Prefect 2016/2017

Experience

Web Back-end Freelancer Dec 2022 - Till date

Sannex Design

Working with a team of web designers to help develop websites for clients home and abroad.

Campus Fellowship Coordinator *Dec* 2021 – *Sept* 2022

Apostolic Faith Campus Fellowship | FCE(T), Akoka

I worked with a team of 4 to carry out the vision of adding value to campus students by hosting exciting programmes and meetings.

Student Intern Jan 2022 - May 2022

Artificial Intelligence and Robotics Lab | University of Lagos

I worked with a team of 7 at the company to learn and build of autonomous and controlled robots with the use of sensors and Arduino Micro-controller.

Senior Prefect (Head Boy) Oct 2017 – Aug 2018

Kolabod Private School | Ijoko-Lemode, Ogun, Nigeria

I worked with senior prefects in my session to plan and organize educative programmes for the students and the school at large.

Punctuality Prefect *Oct 2016 – Aug 2017*

Kolabod Private School | Ijoko-Lemode, Ogun, Nigeria

I worked as a punctuality prefect to develop and retain the act of been punctual in the hearts students by commending the early students and giving penalties to late commers.

Licenses & Certifications

Soft Skills

Jobberman Nigeria

HTML Certified (1014-23540114)

Sololearn

JavaScript Certified (23540114-1024)

Sololearn

PHP Certified (1059-23540114)

Sololearn

Desktop Publishing

Masters Computer College

West African Senior Secondary Certificate

West Africa Examination Council, Nigeria

Skills

- HTML, CSS & JavaScript
- PHP Backend Development
- Arduino Programming
- Time Management
- Team Management
- Emotional Intelligence